Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
The hero's name was Lumiere Silvamillion Clover.
He was later hailed as the first Wizard King, and his story became legend.
느낌이 in the fondant music
風が背中を張って
シスクは糸を伝って
Get its up
目を覚ましてよ
Get out
もう間もなく
I love my dreams and
I love you
Let's start this world
Even I cannot drop this world
All I need is getting strong
We can catch the game
ませないで Your
li ditch my head
ほら似 elders変えて
we can't catch the game
しなすよ というのに
どの陰はみんなだ
we can't catch the game
To be continued...
There's a little bit of danger involved in any decision a person makes.
That said, we should probably escape before I run out of mana.
Which way to the exit?
Flix's ultimate move seems to be working.
They couldn't withstand its power.
I still can't wrap my head around how killer that spell was.
It really saved our asses, though.
The only problem is we got sent all the way down here.
Hey, and thanks for fixing my arm. You're kind of nice after all.
I just wanted us to be even.
I might have one more Dimension Slash in me.
But I can feel that evil mana and key from here. Does that mean Elf Boy's best attack wasn't enough?
I want to jump back in there, but until I have a plan, I'd better wait.
For whatever reason, my darkness magic seemed to be a match for that devil.
I guess all I need to do now is land one final hit on him.
The only other contender we've got is the one guy with no magic at all.
The weapon he's using belongs to Likt. What happened?
After Likt's grimoire changed, it became possible for evil beings to use it.
And then, when it made contact with a different devil, it apparently gained the power of anti-magic.
Oh, crap. I think I'm overdoing it.
You clearly have no control over that ability.
He broke a spear from the other world.
It's supposed to trap light magic and warp space, but none of that worked against him.
Okay!
I don't know what devil you got that special talent from.
Regardless, I suggest you learn your plays.
Word, soul, magic.
Voishul in Amatorian.
Fu toker we also.
Snow it, Agadon.
Thanks for getting me out of there.
Oh, crap. I didn't mean to do that.
Light magic. Light swords of conviction.
Wind magic.
Tornado fag.
Damn.
Just as I thought, our attacks are useless against his abilities.
Even with the four-leaf on our side, we can't win.
There's only one thing left for me to do now.
Here I go.
And this time, it won't be to hurt other people, but to protect them.
Demon light magic.
Light swords of conviction.
It worked.
Ah, yes.
The elf chosen by the four-leaf.
You're on the wrong side, though.
Which means your efforts are utterly wasted.
Everyone else is pushing their limits on their magic.
I need to be able to do that, too.
Should I make it take shape and try to hold it there?
Come on!
Are you alright, your highness?
That really hurt.
Anti-magic is amazing.
I probably won't be able to use my power for a while.
Sounds like you're not alright, then.
It's not very likely to work.
But I can bind it using my sealing magic.
Then maybe I can get control of it.
It'll be fine.
It takes you so long to do everything, Asta.
Hurry up!
If you can't use your power to its full potential,
then how can you ever be...
the Wizard King!
Our magic had dispersed into the air,
but he used his wind to condense it
and made it into a weapon that could combat the darkness.
He's grown significantly stronger over the course of a single battle.
Wind Spirit Creation Magic!
Spirit of Zephyr!
Yeah, yeah.
I was getting there.
I just needed a sec.
See, you can do it if you try.
Of course I can!
Because I'm the guy who's going to be the next Wizard King!
Anti-magic Demon Slayer Sword!
Black Divider!
He's got a wind attribute as well as sword magic!
Yes, that makes sense!
Amazing!
But what about the boy using the five-leaf grimoire?
Who is he?
He's a foolish boy born with no magic,
and he's always barreling into things head-on.
Huh?
That said,
he tries harder than anyone in the kingdom,
and he will never give up!
Stubborn to a fault!
How do you like me now, you big jerk?
I one-upped ya!
I finally gave it shape,
but I don't feel like I can keep it going for much longer.
Hang in there as long as you can.
At least until we cut this guy down.
It'll only take a second.
You're lively, I'll give you that.
But at that speed,
I'm not sure you'll be able to reach me.
That wretched wind magic,
it made him faster!
The anti-magic pursued the wind,
and the wind traveled through the void.
That was a brilliant combination.
They did it.
You putrid trash!
Oh dear!
I'll kill you all!
I pierced his heart,
and then it just popped up somewhere else.
I'll kill you all!
I'm going to exterminate every single one of you!
I think that devil's getting serious now.
He's about to swallow up everything.
So he's been holding back this whole time?
But with all this crap in the way,
we can't get close to him.
This is going poorly even for the best of us.
I'm worried about our allies on the lower floors.
Patry,
defend the perimeter for now.
We'll handle this.
No matter what happens,
we can't let the people of this era be killed.
We need the present-day Magic Knights.
They're the future of the Clover Kingdom.
You think it's over?
You don't get to decide how this ends.
You ready, Yuno?
Let's go!
Of course I'm ready, idiot.
Time to shut this guy up for good!
Not occupies,
you're the mayor.
You're no better thanішers!
A mirroring too senza,
as flown as,
as run Thor as a spider,
Die!
The only atonement is your death.
Not just maggots,
not just your rights!
You首k!
Twist up your arms!
Die!
My kingdom!
Die!!
Die!
The anti-magic is really affecting him.
That's why he avoided that blow to his heart.
And why he's so furious about getting hit.
So that means, if we can get Asta's sword to actually pierce his heart.
Jeff, these things go on forever!
This sucks! My body's starting to reach its limit!
That anti-magic boy. He's fighting side-by-side with the wind magic user and trusting him completely.
They can do this.
We'll leave it to them and help their friends.
Peppered magic!
Almost time! Soon I'll be able to slice this girl's healing magic into tiny pieces!
Wait a second!
We really shouldn't be fighting!
I thought you guys went to a different floor!
No time to explain! This place is about to flood with inhuman magic!
Everyone evacuate! Quickly!
Monosome!
Kali-dos-prachium!
Fire!
Captain Merylione's here too?
I've never seen a spell like that! This world is amazing!
Ew, gross! Where the heck does this nasty-looking purple stuff come from?
Things are getting dire. Oh no! It's catching up!
The demon-dweller sword connects those who have strong bonds, allowing them to share their power.
Since my magic has a chance against the devil, we'll use the sword to send it to everyone.
Combo spell! Demon-dweller sword! Protecting life!
This power! What is it?
Looks like Licht and that prince of yours combined their abilities into one big spell.
How do you know that?
My connection with Licht shows me what's going on above our heads.
Isn't that nice? He got to have a little reunion with his long-lost friend.
Huh. Oh. I gotta say, it makes me feel kinda jealous.
As long as this spell holds, I won't let a single one die.
Demon-like creation matches, Light Whip of Judgment!
The bond they have. This time, I'll trust it.
With the spell acting as a shield, we can focus on our attacks.
Hey! Where'd you get that light from? No fair! Come on! I want one!
I know you get angry any time something proves I'm better than you, but we're in the middle of something!
Fine, pretty boy! Careful, though! You might mess up your hair!
I don't appreciate what I want to die!
You are so close to everything you believe!
It's a sudden you'll see us!
Oh, really?
I hear you!
Just let us!
Keep your distance, human. You're too close to me again.
Hey, if you didn't have me here, you'd be eyeballs deep in that purple crap.
Anyway, didn't you say you could see what's happening on the upper floor?
I'm thinking going by Mana and Ki alone probably isn't the safest strategy for us.
Keep me updated on what that freak's doing, would you? And stop complaining so much.
You're kidding! You think that'll work from here? Well, I'd prefer to be asked more politely, but I'll add momentum to your strike.
You'd better not miss!
I won't!
We'll finish off this battle with an all-out attack!
At first, I only got close to you so that I could use you.
You had no magic, but you happened to obtain the five-leaf grimoire that repelled magic.
And then, the more time I spent around you, the more times I saw you fight, the more I wanted to believe in you.
I wanted to cheer you on.
So, please, win this, Asta!
I can feel this light making me even stronger.
Looks like he's maxed out, though.
Sorry, Asta, but if you can't keep up, I'm ditching you.
You should know that's never gonna happen!
You're just a human, yet you're using Elven and Spirit power to find me!
They'll never pierce through my heart with a silly gust of wind!
Meanwhile, that obnoxious fool is merely letting himself be pulled along by his partner's spell!
And poorly, I might add, they're no danger to me.
Where's the anti-magic boy?
Hiding in the severed magic?
He's approaching from my blind spot!
They're pulling each other in with increasing speed!
Stop!
Be careful!
Go back!
Stop!
That's all I've got!
Now, Asta!
Nice try!
His level of concentration is astounding.
But there's no way he'll succeed from this distance.
You sure about this?
Putting a foreigner like me in charge of a magic knight's squad?
Don't worry.
I'm sure you'll do just fine.
I mean, I'm sure I'll do things my own way.
And I know some of the higher-ups won't be thrilled about it.
Yeah, my magic's kind of rare and all, but still...
I know that.
Yami, I've watched you for a while.
Trust me, you can handle the job.
MonoZone!
Dark-cloaked, Dimension Slash, Equinox!
Dark magic can interfere with the other world.
Curse that human!
I know that key, Captain Yami.
I've hurt you!
Sealing recovery magic!
Heavenly prison!
Faint omen!
I've sealed his physical damage.
Now he just needs to draw out his anti-magic power.
Asta!
Die!
Ferris!
Disappearing!
Ah!
You burn!
You're nothing butali-
Basta!
Master?
Remember….
You are going to be the Wizard King!
Yeah.
Right here, right now, I'm going to push past my limits!
Yeah!
Woo!
You can hear me
Oh wow
Oh!
Thank you.
The battle ends and a new morning comes.